Hello Hello friends, in today's video we will talk about
which companies' life insurance premium
can you pay from the CSC Digital Seva portal and which companies' health
insurance premium can you pay,
what
percentage will you get in it and which company's
premium will you deposit here, we will
cover the complete details for you in this video, stay tuned to
this video and
learn about its entire process, so
simply you have to login to the CSC Digital Seva portal,
after logging in you have to go to the menu bar that you see here, if
you click on Insurance here, a
new interface will
open in front of you like this, you can see here, on the
left side you will get the option of
life insurance premium and health
insurance premium, so let's talk about
which companies' life insurance premium you want to pay, you can
pay for that of
another life insurance here, you can
deposit the premium of Aviva Life, you can pay
for Bajaj Allianz, in the
same way you can pay for Canara HSBC, you can pay for
Exide Life Insurance,
ICICI
Prudential  You can do life insurance, you
can do Kotak Life Insurance, you
can do Life Insurance Corporation, you can do
Shriram Life Insurance, you can do Par
America Life Insurance Company, you can do
HDFC Standard Life, you
can do India First Life Insurance, you can do Max Life Insurance, you
can do SBI Life Insurance, you can do Shriram Life Insurance, you
can do Vivah India, you can do
Future Generali India Life Insurance, you
can do ICICI Prudential Life Insurance, you can do Life Insurance
Corporation also and you can do Star Union, you can do
Tata Sky Life Insurance,
you can pay the premium here,
you have seen the complete details here,
you can pay the
premium of any premium from here, you can
talk about the premium of life insurance,
you can pay the premium of which company from here,
so
you can pay the health insurance premium of Magma HD Insurance, you can do
Max Bupa Health
Insurance, you can pay the premium of Religare Health
Insurance Company Limited
from here, simply
you will have to click on the premium of any company you want to pay,
after that here
You will get the option to make payment here, simply
type the policy number, type the email ID,
enter the mobile number, enter the customer
's mobile number and click on fat bill, the
bill details will appear here,
so enter the amount to be paid
and after that you can directly
subscribe in this
way, if you
want to make payment of life insurance premium, enter the
mobile number of any subscribed customer here and
click, the details will appear, after that you can
subscribe,
you can earn lakhs by paying the premium of medium and health insurance, you get a
good commission, you will
not get such commission from any other company, so the best
option for you will be to make payment, you
can also add it from the CSC Digital Seva Portal,
you can also add it directly from the company's website,
but you will
not get any commission there, you
get a skin when you subscribe, but
subscribe
above,
friends, you must be seeing it in today's video, if you
like it then like it
and if you want to watch videos then you can play, it remains
secret that you will get videos on every topic
about CSC  If
you want to know about the service then you can
subscribe
with any new topic.